<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<textSamples>
    <textSample>
        	<textSampleTitle>What is a Text?</textSampleTitle>
        	<textSampleType>PlainText</textSampleType>
        	<content>IN LITERARY THEORY A TEXT IS ANY OBJECT THAT CAN BE READ WHETHER THIS OBJECT IS A WORK OF LITERATURE A STREET SIGN AN ARRANGEMENT OF BUILDINGS ON A CITY BLOCK OR STYLES OF CLOTHING IT IS A COHERENT SET OF SIGNS THAT TRANSMITS SOME KIND OF INFORMATIVE MESSAGE THIS SET OF SYMBOLS IS CONSIDERED IN TERMS OF THE INFORMATIVE MESSAGES CONTENT RATHER THAN IN TERMS OF ITS PHYSICAL FORM OR THE MEDIUM IN WHICH IT IS REPRESENTED
        	    WITHIN THE FIELD OF LITERARY CRITICISM TEXT ALSO REFERS TO THE ORIGINAL INFORMATION CONTENT OF A PARTICULAR PIECE OF WRITING THAT IS THE TEXT OF A WORK IS THAT PRIMAL SYMBOLIC ARRANGEMENT OF LETTERS AS ORIGINALLY COMPOSED APART FROM LATER ALTERATIONS DETERIORATION COMMENTARY TRANSLATIONS PARATEXT ETC THEREFORE WHEN LITERARY CRITICISM IS CONCERNED WITH THE DETERMINATION OF A TEXT IT IS CONCERNED WITH THE DISTINGUISHING
        	    OF THE ORIGINAL INFORMATION CONTENT FROM WHATEVER HAS BEEN ADDED TO OR SUBTRACTED FROM THAT CONTENT AS IT APPEARS IN A GIVEN TEXTUAL DOCUMENT THAT IS A PHYSICAL REPRESENTATION OF TEXT SINCE THE HISTORY OF WRITING PREDATES THE CONCEPT OF THE TEXT MOST TEXTS WERE NOT WRITTEN WITH THIS CONCEPT IN MIND MOST WRITTEN WORKS FALL WITHIN A NARROW RANGE OF THE textSampleTypeS DESCRIBED BY TEXT THEORY THE CONCEPT OF TEXT BECOMES RELEVANT IF AND WHEN A COHERENT WRITTEN MESSAGE IS COMPLETED AND NEEDS TO BE REFERRED TO INDEPENDENTLY OF THE CIRCUMSTANCES IN WHICH IT WAS CREATED
			 </content>
			 <deletable>0</deletable>    
    </textSample>
	<textSample>
	    	<textSampleTitle>Darwin</textSampleTitle>
	    	<textSampleType>PlainText</textSampleType>
	    	<content>DARWIN PUBLISHED HIS THEORY OF EVOLUTION WITH COMPELLING EVIDENCE IN HIS 1859 BOOK ON THE ORIGIN OF SPECIES, OVERCOMING SCIENTIFIC REJECTION OF EARLIER CONCEPTS OF TRANSMUTATION OF SPECIES. BY THE 1870S THE SCIENTIFIC COMMUNITY AND MUCH OF THE GENERAL PUBLIC HAD ACCEPTED EVOLUTION AS A FACT. HOWEVER, MANY FAVOURED COMPETING EXPLANATIONS AND IT WAS NOT UNTIL THE EMERGENCE OF THE MODERN EVOLUTIONARY SYNTHESIS FROM THE 1930S TO THE 1950S THAT A BROAD CONSENSUS DEVELOPED IN WHICH NATURAL SELECTION WAS THE BASIC MECHANISM OF EVOLUTION.
	    	</content>
	    	<deletable>0</deletable>
	</textSample>
	<textSample>
	    	<textSampleTitle>Hobbit</textSampleTitle>
	    	<textSampleType>PlainText</textSampleType>
	    	<content>DEAD SILENCE FELL IN THE MIDDLE OF A WORD. OUT WENT ALL LIGHT. THE FIRES LEAPED UP IN BLACK SMOKES. ASHES AND CINDERS WERE IN THE EYES OF THE DWARVES, AND THE WOOD WAS FILLED AGAIN WITH THEIR CLAMOUR AND THEIR CRIES.
	    	    BILBO FOUND HIMSELF RUNNING ROUND AND ROUND (AS HE THOUGHT) AND CALLING AND CALLING: “DORI, NORI, ORI, OIN, GLOIN, FILI, KILI, BOMBUR, BIFUR, BOFUR, DWALIN, BALIN, THORIN OAKENSHIELD,” WHILE PEOPLE HE COULD NOT SEE OR FEEL WERE DOING THE SAME ALL ROUND HIM (WITH AN OCCASIONAL “BILBO!” THROWN IN).
	    	</content>
	    	<deletable>0</deletable>
	</textSample>
	<textSample>
	    	<textSampleTitle>The Simpsons</textSampleTitle>
	    	<textSampleType>PlainText</textSampleType>
	    	<content>The Simpsons is an American adult animated sitcom created by Matt Groening for the Fox Broadcasting Company. The series is a satirical depiction of a middle class American lifestyle epitomized by the Simpson family, which consists of Homer, Marge, Bart, Lisa, and Maggie. The show is set in the fictional town of Springfield and parodies American culture, society, television, and many aspects of the human condition.
					 The family was conceived by Groening shortly before a solicitation for a series of animated shorts with the producer James L. Brooks. Groening created a dysfunctional family and named the characters after members of his own family, substituting Bart for his own name. The shorts became a part of The Tracey Ullman Show on April 19, 1987. After a three-season run, the sketch was developed into a half-hour prime time show and was an early hit for Fox, becoming the network's first series to land in the Top 30 ratings in a season (1989–1990)
	    	</content>
	    	<deletable>0</deletable>
	</textSample>
	<textSample>
        	<textSampleTitle>Secret Message 1</textSampleTitle>
        	<textSampleType>EncryptedText</textSampleType>
        	<content>KB XXNXVRTM FWYHVP C HQMN BW RPM AQDXGK VVMI WTR SG FQPX PLVVVQG NAMJ QPVTWM MJ C KAGE HJ CKHQGUMYIG O EILXIK UWSC UG EITOZVYFIEV CR QOBPUKBSH IG E TKHK QFHGB QF EISEIJ QT OAIMLZPU UI CL E TQVQGYGX JGH AU MBKEU HTPN MVRPGYXNL WFOS WXHW SW KBRDLFEKKJQ BYLWRIS1 FWCL WVV CR HSFFFNG UH WHRJKRQGYW ME VSDBM HJ KJS UCZHVDCHUKY FIJUOSTM VSEVSZI LTXYGF FWUG ME VSDBM HJ ZVG BWSLMTCZ RDLF SI VVQ BYWMLO WZ LBBGY KH UH LXTIGGQCNXH       	    
			</content>
			<deletable>0</deletable>    
    </textSample>
    <textSample> 
        	<textSampleTitle>Secret Message 2</textSampleTitle>
        	<textSampleType>EncryptedText</textSampleType>
        	<content>QTK YLOQF JAAUQMOUP IKYB UTPQUGSIK LVOYKK CDUT 80 JURSFAT AL 55 YOSIUUU VQGYP MMV AGXPKS ZOB XGYXYOKB AXVDQTF, FZ COFON H KGSIBD UM MXGABE HLDMT AL ERPAQ AUAQXUBMZO QTK ULDZO XYKYFOGU MXGAB. FNL XZMSB AL ZRNJBZFOVK IGZ PTGSIAC, YBEASQUTN FZ G IOAGK YQRA LR SVRZZHFZY YRZTPKS JVTZ CLPFKYK ZUYQT GTBDOJX. EOUZQ ZOBZ, LBOFNLO FKJQATPZ MIAFHOAV MTK BDUZFAT IV SRHZUKYP TGCB EIBIBZLA FNL OAIRFQY PKFU KOMSHQUI WBMQZ XZJ CXXRLVE. GA QTK LKP UM QTK SXEZ PZQ GNB, TATXZY ZQMXABP ZV FZNHYUZ AEQ SVRZZHFZ XHKSK. HCFKY BGXVMQGUP, EAJE MY ZFD GSBJGUAQX TXOQLKLOL XZJ HJQXPZMTZ, PGIO XE ZOB XKDFE GUA ORHOW KEMQJPQUUU, PFGYQQJ AL QDWIAXL QTK YXZML, JUTLOMRZ XZJ MRDY KOABL QTK PKUZPXX KJLZUTFO KEMXUPQMZPLZ UM QTK TLGTAXUTZ, XXZOLGMO QTK YXZML FFYLIR TLSQX IBOGTB PKUPQRF MAVBIMZLA.
        	</content>
        	<deletable>0</deletable>
    </textSample>
    <textSample>
        	<textSampleTitle>Secret Message 3</textSampleTitle>
        	<textSampleType>EncryptedText</textSampleType>
        	<content>DBS JVSNSS ADUHTA KCF UWBWS UIMCZXBI WCBUYHZN SXIKC IC UFTI 51 SM O GMWIHT LONORPWYBI WP YRLIBXG PQB ZCGKO VOHM, GCHWQX NVT VOPOSI DYGI IXX HGISHWCO BUBVM. KWQDZNCBV BY NVT KOHHGIV CBIMVFWVMXWS POOHQN (KSU), HWM MIFGMMN BPUOM TDZ DBS UIMCZXBI UFT PYGSN ISLDDZD (CQPW: URHP) IXX UGWYG ZPSO, NVDCQB HWM XUAT IBYO 51 LIC OGTL SH O RQK XCRCWYBI NBIA IPO PWTBXUA LIB. IHWMB HOBMC OGTL PIF IPO ZORQVCHN QXWZJLO XFTIWFOCL, KHR CQMEBPUOM DPZKXWHM BUBRP, RIAT JKMS PVN QOIMBNCLV
        	</content>
        	<deletable>0</deletable>
        
    </textSample>
	<textSample>
        	<textSampleTitle>Secret Message 4</textSampleTitle>
        	<textSampleType>EncryptedText</textSampleType>
        	<content>Frg gurbel vf gur oenapu bs zngurzngvpny ybtvp gung fghqvrf frgf, juvpu ner pbyyrpgvbaf bs bowrpgf. Nygubhtu nal glcr bs bowrpg pna or pbyyrpgrq vagb n frg, frg gurbel vf nccyvrq zbfg bsgra gb bowrpgf gung ner eryrinag gb zngurzngvpf. Gur ynathntr bs frg gurbel pna or hfrq va gur qrsvavgvbaf bs arneyl nyy zngurzngvpny bowrpgf. Gur zbqrea fghql bs frg gurbel jnf vavgvngrq ol Trbet Pnagbe naq Evpuneq Qrqrxvaq va gur 1870f. Nsgre gur qvfpbirel bs cnenqbkrf va anvir frg gurbel, ahzrebhf nkvbz flfgrzf jrer cebcbfrq va gur rneyl gjragvrgu praghel, bs juvpu gur Mrezryb–Senraxry nkvbzf, jvgu gur nkvbz bs pubvpr, ner gur orfg-xabja.
        	</content>
        	<deletable>0</deletable>
    </textSample>
    
    
	
	
</textSamples>